...Menogias, where have you been?
Menogias, nerelerdeydin?
Brother Yaksha, you're confused again
Yaksha kardeşim, yine karıştırdın.
I've told you countless times, I am Boyang
Sana kaç kere söyledim? Boyang'ım ben.
A thaumaturge who fought with you in The Chasm
Kanyon'da senin yanında savaşan bir efsuncuyum.
Boyang...? Boyang?
Boyang? Boyang mı?
You are Boyang, but who am I?
Sen Boyang'san ben kimim?
Believe me, I wanna know as much as you do
İnan bana, ben de en az senin kadar merak ediyorum bunu.
Here we are, the two who agreed to stay here together
İkimiz birlikte burada kalmaya karar vermiştik.
And I can't even call you by your name
Ama adını bile bilmiyorum.
It's a shame
Çok yazık...
...Stay here?
Burada kalmaya mı?
No, no, you have to leave
Hayır, olmaz, gitmelisin.
Nonsense, Brother Yaksha
Saçmalama Yaksha kardeşim.
We're down here for good now, don't you remember?
Artık buradan çıkamayız, unuttun mu?
...It's too late to have regrets!
Pişmanlık duymak için çok geç!
The seal can't be broken...
Mühür kırılamaz...
...The seal... ah, yes
Mühür... Ah, evet...
I'm... a yaksha who came here to fight
Ben... Buraya savaşmak için gelen bir Yakshayım.
...Brother, brother! Are you okay?
Kardeş, kardeş! İyi misin?
...Haha, look at the state of me. I don't think I've got long now!
Haha, şu halime bak. Fazla zamanım kalmadı.
We're the only two left. Don't go dying on me!
Bir tek ikimiz kaldık. Ölüp beni terk etme!
...You know, today I saw my family down here, clear as day
Bugün ailemi gördüm burada, o kadar netti ki...
What do you think, am I losing my mind now, too?
Ne dersin? Ben de mi aklımı kaybetmeye başladım?
Boyang, do you want to go home?
Boyang, eve gitmek istiyor musun?
I made my decision to leave Rongzhao up on the surface, I obviously...
Rongzhao'yu yüzeyde bırakmaya karar verdim, tabii ki...
Of course I want to go home
Tabii ki eve gitmek istiyorum.
...I must have family, too
Benim de bir ailem olmalı.
You mean, brothers and sisters? I'm sure you do
Kardeşlerin mi? Eminim vardır.
Brothers and sisters...
Kardeşlerim...
Yes, but who am I? And where is my family?
Evet ama ben kimim? Benim ailem nerede?
Hang in there... It's just you and me, don't...
Sakın pes etme... Sadece ikimiz kaldık, sakın...
Don't die before me...
Benden önce öleyim deme...
...Alatus... Is that you?
Alatus... Sen misin?
Who's Alatus? Your memory's going again... ugh...
Alatus kim? Hafızan yine gidiyor...
...I'm sorry you all have to see me in this state
Beni bu halde görmek zorunda kaldığın için özür dilerim.
Brother... Brother!
Kardeş... Kardeş!
...Look... There's someone over there...
Bak... Şurada birisi var...
Who are they...
Onlar da kim?
They're... they're my... my...
Onlar... Onlar benim... Benim...
I remember now, I know you...
Şimdi hatırladım. Seni tanıyorum...
...My brothers and sisters have come for me, Boyang
Kardeşlerim benim için geldi Boyang.
You're... you're awake?
Sen... Uyandın mı?
At least... at least tell me your name!
En azından... En azından bana adını söyle!
Brother!
Kardeşim!
Brother Bosacius!
Bosacius Abi!
Hey, Bosacius!
Selam Bosacius!
Bosacius
Bosacius.
I...
Ben...
I am Bosacius
Ben Bosacius'ım.
And my destiny
Benim kaderimde
Is to make the ultimate sacrifice
son fedakarlığı yapmak yazılı.